<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jobs on Paperchain Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jobs on Paperchain Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 15:27:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Post: Finance Lead (DeFi/Institutional)</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-03-10-job-post-finance-lead-defi-institutional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 15:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-03-10-job-post-finance-lead-defi-institutional/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paperchain is the easiest and fastest way for creators to access their streaming revenue. We’re creating the future of media payments through our unique learning model that prices media streaming activity in near real-time and data integrations with the world’s largest streaming services, such as Spotify, Apple and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Data Engineer (Go, GCP, SQL, Python). Remote OK.</title>
      <link>/post/2019-08-05-hiring-data-engineer-remote-ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 10:06:02 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-08-05-hiring-data-engineer-remote-ok/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paperchain is an early-stage startup building real-time revenue forecasting and financial tools for the digital media industry using unique applications of data science and blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a Data Engineer to come in and help build our data pipeline foundations at Paperchain. This is a contractor role with the plan to transition into a full-time role. The core team functions remotely with HQ being in New York and our CTO in Berlin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Data Analyst - Contractor (R, Google Cloud, Python). Remote OK.</title>
      <link>/post/2019-03-31-hiring-data-analyst-contractor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 10:06:02 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-03-31-hiring-data-analyst-contractor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paperchain is an early-stage startup building real-time revenue forecasting and financial tools for the digital media industry using unique applications of data science and blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a looking for a contractor Data Analyst to help build the data onboarding and analytics process for our first customers. This is a contractor role with the plan to transition into a full-time role.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>